<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-09-06T21:32:59-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/09/06/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2017-09-06T21:09:12-07:00</published><updated>2017-09-06T21:09:12-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/09/06/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/09/06/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;Chickpea’s blog is the best. You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chickpea’s blog is the best. You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Power of Credit Score</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/financial/fitness/2017/09/06/power-of-credit-score.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Power of Credit Score" /><published>2017-09-06T21:09:12-07:00</published><updated>2017-09-06T21:09:12-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/financial/fitness/2017/09/06/power-of-credit-score</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/financial/fitness/2017/09/06/power-of-credit-score.html">&lt;p&gt;I will tell you all about a credit score.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I will tell you all about a credit score.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to interpret your credit score</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/financial/fitness/2017/09/06/interpret-your-credit-score.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to interpret your credit score" /><published>2017-09-06T21:09:12-07:00</published><updated>2017-09-06T21:09:12-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/financial/fitness/2017/09/06/interpret-your-credit-score</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/financial/fitness/2017/09/06/interpret-your-credit-score.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Question #1:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you know your credit score?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Question #2:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you know how to monitor your credit score, for free?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Question #3:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you know how to improve your credit score?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Question #4:&lt;/strong&gt; Do you know why your credit score matters?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you answered “yes” to all of the above, skip this article. If you missed one to all, please skim. Your wallet will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your credit score is how banks and strangers judge your financial fitness. Anyone from a credit card company to a landlord to a prospective spouse may want to know your score. They want to determine your ability to repay debt. You want your score to be really, really good. When you apply for a car loan or a mortgage, you will get a lower interest rate the higher your score. Think of it as walking into a store: prices for identical items differ from person to person. A person with a 780 score gets to buy the shirt for $20. The person with the 520 credit score has to pay $70.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Credit scores range from 300 to 850, however the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.doughroller.net/credit/a-rare-glimpse-inside-the-fico-credit-score-formula/&quot;&gt;exact scoring methodology&lt;/a&gt; is proprietary. Where does your score fall, and what does that mean?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;800+:&lt;/strong&gt; Insanely good. Make this your reach goal, but don’t stress it. I have perfect payment history but don’t fall in this bucket, due to the “young” age of my various credit accounts and the fact that I am not making a house or car payment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;740 - 800:&lt;/strong&gt; You are rockin’ it. You should be able to access the widest variety of debt products and lowest interest rates with a score in this range. You’ve never been late on a payment, and you don’t overuse your credit lines.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;680 - 740:&lt;/strong&gt; Not a bad starting place, but you will likely be approved for higher interest rate debt than your peers with better scores (think: larger monthly payments).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;600 - 680:&lt;/strong&gt; The word here might be “mehhh”. Not good, but not terrible. You probably have a couple blemishes on your credit report. Either, too many inquiries and/or a late payment here and there. You might be maxing out some of your credit cards. You will want to try and clean up your credit act. With this score, some types of credit are no longer available to you, such as a home equity line of credit (a second mortgage on your house). You will definitely be paying a premium to access debt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;500 - 600:&lt;/strong&gt; This is not a zone you want to be in. This is widely considered to be “bad credit.” You will have much fewer debt options, and all the options will be super expensive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sub 500:&lt;/strong&gt; Get the heck out of here as quickly as possible. You likely want to speak to a credit counselor to figure out ways to improve your score quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn about how to check your credit score here.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Question #1: Do you know your credit score? Question #2: Do you know how to monitor your credit score, for free? Question #3: Do you know how to improve your credit score? Question #4: Do you know why your credit score matters?</summary></entry></feed>